happili.com 2012-07-08

# Happili - privacy_policy

We at LJC Media are committed to respecting your online privacy and recognize your need for appropriate protection and management of any information you share with us by using our web sites. 

LJC Media has established the following Privacy Policy so that you can understand the care with which we intend to treat your information. This policy describes the overall privacy practices of LJC Media regarding information we collect on our network of web sites. This policy does not apply to the practices of companies that LJC Media does not own or control, or to people that LJC Media does not employ. 

### Information Collected by LJC Media

LJC Media collects various types of information from you to better meet your needs and to provide you with a more relevant user experience. Some of this information is collected automatically through cookies (a small text file placed on your computer) or other Internet tracking technologies. The type of information your browser or Internet session may automatically provide us with can include the browser you are using, your Internet domain, the operating system on your computer, your IP address and the URL you saw just before coming to the LJC Media site, the pages of the site you visited and the URL of the page you visited upon leaving the site. 

LJC Media may also contract with reputable third-party advertising companies to serve ads on our behalf. These companies may also use cookies or other measures to collect your non-personally identifiable information. 

In addition, at some of the LJC Media web sites, we collect information that you may choose to provide to us when requesting additional information from us or from one or more of our clients. Examples of personally identifiable data that you may provide to us include name, address, and email address. If you provide personally identifiable data to us, you may later elect to have your information deleted from our files, or kept from being used for purposes other than for the service requested, by following the opt-out procedures set forth below. 

### How Collected Information is Used

The non-personally identifiable information that LJC Media collects is used for marketing and sales efforts to better target advertisements and other content in an effort to create a more personally relevant experience. The information is also used to predict responses to advertisements, and to help determine which ads perform best and which content is most appropriate for different individuals. 

All personally identifiable information you provide is maintained in confidence by LJC Media. LJC Media may share your information as necessary to comply with a court order or to cooperate with government and law enforcement officials. 

### Security

Wherever your personally identifiable information may be held within LJC Media or on its behalf, we intend to take reasonable and appropriate steps to protect the information you shared with us from unauthorized access or disclosure. Please note that while LJC Media will make every reasonable effort to protect your information, no transmission of data over the Internet is 100% secure. 

### Choice

Some of our web sites utilize cookies to collect information about your website activities and to recall the personal information you previously shared with us. Most browsers allow you to control cookies, including whether or not to accept them and how to remove them. 

You may set most browsers to notify you if you receive a cookie, or you may choose to block cookies with your browser. Blocking cookies may result in a lower quality experience for you while you are visiting LJC Media web sites. 

### Your California Privacy Rights

California has passed legislation requiring certain specific disclosures be made available to California residents who use the Internet and provide information that may be used for marketing purposes. That legislation requires any business that discloses a customer's personal information (as defined by the act) to any third party for direct marketing purposes to provide the customer a method for obtaining the names, addresses and certain other specified details of anyone who might have received that personal information. 

If you are a California resident you may request this information from LJC Media or any of its affiliates by contacting us here. LJC Media is not obligated to respond to more than one such request from a customer per calendar year. 

### Commitment

Protecting your privacy online is an evolving area, and LJC Media's web sites are constantly changing to meet these demands. 

If you have any comments or questions regarding our Online Privacy Policy, please contact us here. While we cannot guarantee privacy perfection, we will address any issue to the best of our abilities as soon as practicable after you bring it to our attention. 

### Your Consent

By using this web site, you consent to the terms of our Privacy Policy and to LJC Media's processing of personally identifiable information for the purposes given above. Should the Online Privacy Policy change, we intend to take every reasonable step to ensure that these changes are brought to your attention by posting all changes prominently on our web site for a reasonable period of time and by amending this privacy policy. 

### Contacting Us

For more information, or if you have questions or concerns regarding LJC Media's Privacy Policy, you may contact us here.
